adwarealert.com 2010-11-25

# Adware Alert Respects Your Privacy

AdwareAlert.com, Inc is committed to the privacy of personal information provided to us when using any of our Internet services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat information we receive when you transmit data to AdwareAlert.com Internet properties. 

**Web Information**   
When you purchase AdwareAlert.com software, we may collect personal identifiable information including your name, address, email address, etc. for the purpose of recording and fulfilling the transaction. When we use a payment processing merchant we ensure that the same strict privacy criterion is in place. We do not (knowingly) collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen. 

**Cookies**   
We define a cookie as any string of data and information that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our services. AdwareAlert.com employs cookies to assign non-unique, non-identifiable strings to machines that access our services. This information enables us to deliver faster service capabilities to our customers or to our affiliates, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All AdwareAlert.com cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to AdwareAlert.com, 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information and 5) non-unique. Our Cookies are mainly maintained to track our affiliates to ensure proper payments for their sales and tracking activities relating to their affiliate relationship with us. 

**Security**   
The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain such safeguards to protect security of servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, thwart fraud, provide customer service, or maintain your account with us. 

**How Information Is Used When Collected**   
We may use information in the following ways:   
\- For purposes you specifically provided the information such as to enable us to process, validate and verify purchases.   
\- To register you as a customer and open and maintain a support account for you.   
\- To send email notifications about new, existing, enhanced products or services. Information on special offers, or to contact you to reconfirm or verify accuracy of information provided.   
\- To obtain your feedback to help enhance existing features or provide additional products and services.   
We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example protect our intellectual property rights). We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law may require us to do so. 

**AdwareAlert**

**What Information AdwareAlert Collects**   
AdwareAlert Software does not collect any personal identifiable information from your computer. A log is created of items detected for removal on your computer abd remains on your harddrive for your referance. During a support situation this log may be requested for troubleshooting by a support tech but requires the user to manually send.  
AdwareAlert application Does NOT send information about you or your computer to anyone. 

**AntiSpywareNet Threat Watch CONTRIBUTIONS and PRIVACY**

If you choose to join the opt-in AntiSpyware Threat Watch community, our software will check areas in your computer where malware commonly runs against a master database in order to see if the file is recognized. In order to perform these checks, our software may query our servers during scheduled scans about these files to see if they are already identified. If a file is unrecognized and/or found to show malicious behavior it is anonymously uploaded to our servers to be analyzed by our team of researchers. When malware is found by this process it is added to our threat database. If no malware is found in an uploaded file, the file signature is added to an ignore list and deleted from our servers.

The scope of the Threat Watch Scan is limited to running processes such as dll's and exe's and does not include personal files such as documents, images, ect. You can opt-out of the AntiSpywareNet Threat Watch community at any time by un-checking the "Upload Suspicious Files to AntiSpywareNet” in the settings menu

**Updates**   
Your copy of AdwareAlert, once installed, will check in with our server occasionally to receive threat database update. The only value transmitted to the server is the current version of the software.   
You can control the way updates are performed through Settings dialog. By default updates are performed after confirmed notification of engine update available. 

**Policy Modifications**   
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. However, any changes will be posted promptly here, so please check back periodically. 

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at support@adwarealert.com.
